[{"answer": "Well first of all, let's look at the context.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "What is your take on what has gone down today with him and his girlfriend?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Because you can imagine sitting down and having a beer with him and he's not going to judge you, and he loves football.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Why is that I feel myself warming to him?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think personal feeling for most politicians is smoking crack.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "But if that was a criteria for being a politician, I mean almost all of them would have to give up their jobs, wouldn't they?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "You ever got drunk before, Bill?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Well, I was part of the agenda.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "What changed your mind?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Well, he retains some statutory powers that are conferred to him by the province.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Can he stumble on as a figure head or is this the beginning of the end do you feel?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "Vindicated is such an empty feeling.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Do you feel now vindicated by events, so in a sense it's probably much more plausible what you claim for given his way he's been admitting stuff?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "I think he is.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "Is he hurting Toronto?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Well, the businesses aren't saying it's not.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "If that guy is the mayor, what's the rest of them like?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "I think it is.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "Is he damaging Toronto?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "He was completely stoned.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Was he just being rambunctious Rob Ford or was he being a very unpleasant harasser in your view?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "No comment.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Did he see toes?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "I think it's all about Toronto and I think we have to start thinking about Toronto.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "What do you say to that charge?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "I don't think a lot of the media is saying he's damaging Toronto.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "A lot of other people are thinking, \"Wow, this is all quite fun,\" isn't it?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "I think he's exceptionally good at setting a conservative tone.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Has he been a quite effective mayor as he claims?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "He's been claiming that he saved a billion dollars, city government costs of rate has gone up $200 million.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "So, do you think -- but Sarah he's been achieving that and keeping a good, tight fist on the expenditure, who cares if he gets drunk occasionally?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "He's quite naughty.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Is he that naughty?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Yeah, he'll cling.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "He can survive this?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Terrific.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "It's brutal.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "How brutal is a Presidential campaign?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "The best moment is seeing the people.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "And what was the worst moment?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "Well, you know, the election night I have to say it was pretty darn low.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Outside of the moment you lost obviously, what was the lowest moment of the whole thing?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "I was getting nervous on election day.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Did you go into that night and genuinely thinking you could still pull it off?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Well, you know, he's put himself in a very sticky place because you either have to think that he was not telling the truth or he's grossly incompetent.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "And in particular the President's position that he's found himself in?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "I think a little bit of both.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Which side are you leaning towards?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "I don't think he was telling the truth.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "You think he lied?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "It's the same thing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "A fluffernutter.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "What's it called?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "If he absolutely.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Is he is the type of candidate?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "I hope not.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "You wouldn't be having many of these if runs, will he?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Fluffernutters.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "The -- what are they called again?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "ORGAN: This has your -- one of your grandchildren?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "That's me and ...", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Oh, you're son?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "There's also lovely pictures in here of you, your kids, your grandkids, and so on.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Well, you know, wouldn't it be nice if we could always stay as young as, you know, we were in our 20s?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "You know, I'd love to see a lot of more women involved in politics.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Would you like to see a woman president regardless of which party?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "Have you ever attempted to run?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "For any high office?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "ORGAN: Really?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "My Welsh -- Annie Evans.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "It's a recipe from your Welsh grandmother, Annie Evans?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Kieran Matthew.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "Now, you have a new addition to the family, Kieran James Romney?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "He is about 6 months old now because we didn't legally adopt him.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "And he's -- how old is he?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "You know, I'd advised him that this is not a good time in their lives that they need to ...", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Anything?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "... some of these even I could do, yeah.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "You can do it?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "Refalca did well.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "What happened to Refalca?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "She's -- I'm riding on her occasionally myself now but, you know, horses has been part of my therapy for me to getting stronger.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "Where is Refalca?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "Warren Buffett really is, the one on one business and just a stakeholder to the point that not make things too difficult very -- very -- very straightforward and -- that's why I like him, and I just click very well with him.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "In other words you can never do a good deal with a bad guy, and that with many people, a handshake is good enough for him?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "I have a lot of respect and have a lot of confidence for the US economy, no doubt about that.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "Do you still feel confident in the way the American economy is going or do you share concerns that many people have that it's--it could potentially if they're not careful rebound back into some kind of recession?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "Why did you like Twitter so much?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "I think he means, you know, you're quite often get seen with very large palaces and yachts and all that kinds of things.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 716, "question": "And what does he mean by that?", "qSentId": 715}, {"answer": "Yeah, as Mr. Netanyahu said that you really find the majority of the Arab World in complete sync and alliance with the concepts of Israel.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 733, "question": "One of the great players in the Middle East, what do you make of what's going on here, with this tension now between -- clear tension between Netanyahu and what he believes is going on with Iran and the America and everybody else?", "qSentId": 732}, {"answer": "IN TALAL: It's not that it's trust.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 738, "question": "Do you trust Assad when he says he'll give up his chemical weapons?", "qSentId": 737}, {"answer": "That's a very good question.", "docId": "131118pmt", "aSentId": 749, "question": "Giving people back in Saudi Arabia fully understand the dangers of what is going on here?", "qSentId": 748}]